[
  {
    "Article": "Shibboleth Authentication Request",
    "Article URL": "https://link-springer-com.ucd.idm.oclc.org/article/10.1007/s10814-021-09157-1#Sec22",
    "Question": "\\{\\{0:None\\}\\}",
    "Answer": "None"
  },
  {
    "Article": "G7 ministers to discuss far-reaching deal on corporate tax",
    "Article URL": "https://www.irishtimes.com/business/economy/g7-ministers-to-discuss-far-reaching-deal-on-corporate-tax-1.4583263",
    "Question": "The US is leading calls for an agreement at the Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development (OECD) on a major overhaul of \\{\\{0:corporate tax rules\\}\\}, a process which threatens \\{\\{1:Irish tax revenue\\}\\} and also the use of a low tax regime to attract \\{\\{2:multinationals\\}\\}.",
    "Answer": "corporate tax rules, Irish tax revenue, multinationals"
  },
  {
    "Article": "G7 ministers to discuss far-reaching deal on corporate tax",
    "Article URL": "https://www.irishtimes.com/business/economy/g7-ministers-to-discuss-far-reaching-deal-on-corporate-tax-1.4583263",
    "Question": "The Minister for Finance Paschal Donohoe, will attend the meeting, which starts on Friday, in his role as president of the Eurogroup of finance ministers and will discuss \\{\\{0:corporate tax\\}\\} at a \\{\\{1:bilateral meeting\\}\\} on Saturday with \\{\\{2:US treasury secretary\\}\\}, Janet Yellen.",
    "Answer": "corporate tax, bilateral meeting, US treasury secretary"
  },
  {
    "Article": "G7 ministers to discuss far-reaching deal on corporate tax",
    "Article URL": "https://www.irishtimes.com/business/economy/g7-ministers-to-discuss-far-reaching-deal-on-corporate-tax-1.4583263",
    "Question": "UK focus\nMr Sunak, has underlined the UK’s focus on the part of \\{\\{0:the global \\{\\{1:tax\\}\\} reform agenda\\}\\} relating to \\{\\{2:big multinationals\\}\\} paying tax in markets where they sell via the imposition of a digital sales tax.",
    "Answer": "the global tax reform agenda, tax, big multinationals"
  },
  {
    "Article": "G7 ministers to discuss far-reaching deal on corporate tax",
    "Article URL": "https://www.irishtimes.com/business/economy/g7-ministers-to-discuss-far-reaching-deal-on-corporate-tax-1.4583263",
    "Question": "This would reduce the amount of tax which some big players pay in Ireland with the Department of \\{\\{1:Finance\\}\\} pencilling in a possible revenue loss of up to €2 billion per annum, out of \\{\\{2:total corporate tax revenue\\}\\} of almost €12 billion.",
    "Answer": "part, Finance, total corporate tax revenue"
  },
  {
    "Article": "G7 ministers to discuss far-reaching deal on corporate tax",
    "Article URL": "https://www.irishtimes.com/business/economy/g7-ministers-to-discuss-far-reaching-deal-on-corporate-tax-1.4583263",
    "Question": "The ministers look certain to signal support for a deal and reports on Thursday evening pointed to efforts to achieve a breakthrough on key details, including \\{\\{0:a global minimum \\{\\{1:corporate tax\\}\\} rate\\}\\} of 15 per cent, above the Republic’s 12.5 per \\{\\{2:cent rate\\}\\}.",
    "Answer": "a global minimum corporate tax rate, corporate tax, cent rate"
  },
  {
    "Article": "G7 ministers to discuss far-reaching deal on corporate tax",
    "Article URL": "https://www.irishtimes.com/business/economy/g7-ministers-to-discuss-far-reaching-deal-on-corporate-tax-1.4583263",
    "Question": "Photograph: Hollie Adams/EPA\nFinance ministers from the main industrialised countries are set to discuss a deal on the reform of \\{\\{0:the global \\{\\{1:corporate tax\\}\\} system\\}\\} , including a minimum tax rate for \\{\\{2:multinationals\\}\\}, at a G7 meeting in London this weekend.",
    "Answer": "the global corporate tax system, corporate tax, multinationals"
  },
  {
    "Article": "G7 ministers to discuss far-reaching deal on corporate tax",
    "Article URL": "https://www.irishtimes.com/business/economy/g7-ministers-to-discuss-far-reaching-deal-on-corporate-tax-1.4583263",
    "Question": "Donohoe to meet with \\{\\{0:US treasury secretary\\}\\} at \\{\\{1:bilateral meeting\\}\\} on \\{\\{2:Saturday\\}\\}",
    "Answer": "US treasury secretary, bilateral meeting, Saturday"
  },
  {
    "Article": "G7 ministers to discuss far-reaching deal on corporate tax",
    "Article URL": "https://www.irishtimes.com/business/economy/g7-ministers-to-discuss-far-reaching-deal-on-corporate-tax-1.4583263",
    "Question": "The ante has been upped ahead of the meeting by a decision by the \\{\\{0:US\\}\\} to apply tariffs on $2 billion of imports from Austria, India, Italy, Spain, Turkey and the UK in retaliation for these countries implementing their own digital services taxes on \\{\\{2:US multinationals\\}\\}.",
    "Answer": "US, tax, US multinationals"
  },
  {
    "Article": "Stephen Collins: What price Irish neutrality in today's world?",
    "Article URL": "https://www.irishtimes.com/opinion/stephen-collins-what-price-irish-neutrality-in-today-s-world-1.4583398",
    "Question": "Nowadays \\{\\{0:UN peacekeeping operations\\}\\} are often subcontracted out to \\{\\{1:Nato\\}\\} or the \\{\\{2:EU\\}\\}.",
    "Answer": "UN peacekeeping operations, Nato, EU"
  },
  {
    "Article": "Stephen Collins: What price Irish neutrality in today's world?",
    "Article URL": "https://www.irishtimes.com/opinion/stephen-collins-what-price-irish-neutrality-in-today-s-world-1.4583398",
    "Question": "In 1999 Ireland joined the \\{\\{0:Nato\\}\\} partnership for peace and more recently we have engaged with moves towards \\{\\{2:closer European defence arrangements\\}\\}.",
    "Answer": "Nato, part, closer European defence arrangements"
  },
  {
    "Article": "Stephen Collins: What price Irish neutrality in today's world?",
    "Article URL": "https://www.irishtimes.com/opinion/stephen-collins-what-price-irish-neutrality-in-today-s-world-1.4583398",
    "Question": "\\{\\{0:Close defence co\\}\\}-\\{\\{1:operation\\}\\} with our fellow \\{\\{2:EU\\}\\} member states is an important statement of the nation’s values and is also vital for its future security",
    "Answer": "Close defence co, operation, EU"
  },
  {
    "Article": "Stephen Collins: What price Irish neutrality in today's world?",
    "Article URL": "https://www.irishtimes.com/opinion/stephen-collins-what-price-irish-neutrality-in-today-s-world-1.4583398",
    "Question": "The answer to both is that close \\{\\{0:defence co\\}\\}-\\{\\{1:operation\\}\\} with our fellow \\{\\{2:EU\\}\\} member states is an important statement of the nation’s values and is also vital for its future security.",
    "Answer": "defence co, operation, EU"
  },
  {
    "Article": "Stephen Collins: What price Irish neutrality in today's world?",
    "Article URL": "https://www.irishtimes.com/opinion/stephen-collins-what-price-irish-neutrality-in-today-s-world-1.4583398",
    "Question": "The Department of Foreign Affairs in its submission to the Commission on \\{\\{0:Defence\\}\\} has stressed that closer co-\\{\\{1:operation\\}\\} with the European Defence Agency and \\{\\{2:Nato\\}\\} is increasingly important.",
    "Answer": "Defence, operation, Nato"
  },
  {
    "Article": "Stephen Collins: What price Irish neutrality in today's world?",
    "Article URL": "https://www.irishtimes.com/opinion/stephen-collins-what-price-irish-neutrality-in-today-s-world-1.4583398",
    "Question": "The need for a full public discussion about these issues is long overdue so that the debate is not hijacked by small vocal groups who oppose any form of \\{\\{0:defence co\\}\\}-\\{\\{2:operation\\}\\} with our neighbours.",
    "Answer": "defence co, -, operation"
  },
  {
    "Article": "Stephen Collins: What price Irish neutrality in today's world?",
    "Article URL": "https://www.irishtimes.com/opinion/stephen-collins-what-price-irish-neutrality-in-today-s-world-1.4583398",
    "Question": "Polls show majority of \\{\\{0:voters\\}\\} in \\{\\{1:favour\\}\\} of \\{\\{2:closer EU defence and security arrangements\\}\\}",
    "Answer": "voters, favour, closer EU defence and security arrangements"
  },
  {
    "Article": "Stephen Collins: What price Irish neutrality in today's world?",
    "Article URL": "https://www.irishtimes.com/opinion/stephen-collins-what-price-irish-neutrality-in-today-s-world-1.4583398",
    "Question": "A number of \\{\\{0:recent opinion polls\\}\\} have shown a clear majority of voters in \\{\\{1:favour\\}\\} of \\{\\{2:closer EU defence and security arrangements\\}\\}.",
    "Answer": "recent opinion polls, favour, closer EU defence and security arrangements"
  }
]